<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-05-17T04:26:12.074Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-05-17T04:26:12.074Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.7.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writing a simple JSON Parser from scratch in C++]]></title>
        <id>https://kishoreganesh.com/post/writing-a-json-parser-in-cplusplus/</id>
        <link href="https://kishoreganesh.com/post/writing-a-json-parser-in-cplusplus/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T14:43:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JSON is one of the most common data interchange formats there is. Thankfully, it is also a pretty simple one. I had written a JSON parser in C++ sometime back, and whilst making it I came across a few decisions that were more involved than I thought they would be. So I have decided to write an article around that JSON Parser. While JSON Parsing is simple, writing one would definitely be useful to build more complex parsers, since the general principles are still present.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kishore Ganesh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taking away control: The dumb programmer and the smart compiler]]></title>
        <id>https://kishoreganesh.com/post/programming_languages/</id>
        <link href="https://kishoreganesh.com/post/programming_languages/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T20:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good compilers prevent you from shooting yourself in the foot. Today, you have a wide assortment of programming languages to choose from, you can have your pick of paradigm. As a brief detour, the perspective of programmers comes full circle as they move from beginner to slightly experienced to intermediate.
The beginner is deathly afraid of the differences between programming languages. In the beginning, they stick to one language out of the fear of learning something new.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kishore Ganesh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[bootup]]></title>
        <id>https://kishoreganesh.com/post/bootup/</id>
        <link href="https://kishoreganesh.com/post/bootup/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T19:28:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A long, long time back, in a galaxy far far away, I was doing the same thing I’m doing right now. Booting up a blog. Genesis. Creation. My older blogs are many years behind me, and now a new journey begins.
I have witnessed a stark change in how I view blogging, or how I view writing in general over my 4 years of college. More on that in a later post, but I’m excited to embark on this new journey, incorporating the many insights hidden away in some deep dark corner of my Google Keep.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kishore Ganesh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My experience at eyrc 2020-21]]></title>
        <id>60855d25c8fa47657c19ee85</id>
        <link href="https://manav.co.in/my-experience-at-eyrc-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-25T13:01:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[an amazing experience]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manav Sethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>